https://americanwoodmark.com/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyThe purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you, as a user of our site, of what kinds of information we gather about you, and how we use and/or disclose it. Please note that you may link to other sites from this one, or you may have been linked to this site from another site; this privacy policy does not apply to information collected about you during your visit to such linked sites.Information You SubmitDuring your correspondence with us that originates from this site, we may collect personal information about you such as your email address or other information that you choose to supply. We may request certain information from you in order to provide customer service to you, but you may always choose to respond electronically or not. We will use any information that you submit only to reply to your email or customer service request. We might also use that information to let you know of our other products or services in which you may be interested.DisclosureWe do not sell or disclose information about your individual visits to our site or information that you might give us through the site, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies; however, if you send us an inquiry relating to our products purchased through one of our business partners, we reserve the right to disclose such information to the business partner that sold your our products for customer service purposes. We may also share such information: (a) with our business partners to help communicate with you about offers from us; (b) during legal procedures such as subpoenas and court orders; (c) if we merge with or are acquired by a third party; or (d) in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms, or as otherwise required by law.Changes to Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes here. You should periodically check this policy because your use of the site after any changes are posted will indicate that you have accepted any changes.
NEW
APPLICANTS
Explore Jobs
Current
Employees
Find Openings
Student
Programs
